
[
  { "question":"Who was the first featured character banner in genshin?",
    "correct_answer":"Venti",
    "difficulty":"Medium",
    "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which Element has the most characters?",
    "correct_answer":"Cryo",
    "difficulty":"Medium",
    "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"How many playable cryo characters are in the game as of 4.3?",
    "correct_answer":"15",
    "difficulty":"Medium",
    "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What element and weapon combination is missing from the playable characters?",
    "correct_answer":"Hydro Claymore",
    "difficulty":"Medium",
    "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which Element has the least playable characters?",
    "correct_answer":"Dendro",
    "difficulty":"Medium",
    "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is the name of the 'umbrella' weapon?",
    "correct_answer":"Toukabou Shigure",
    "difficulty":"Medium",
    "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What does Pyro resonance do?",
    "correct_answer":"+25% atk",
    "difficulty":"Easy",
    "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who killed la signora?",
    "correct_answer":"Raiden Shogun",
    "difficulty":"Easy",
    "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who is Klees mother?",
    "correct_answer":"Alice",
    "difficulty":"Easy",
    "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is Fischls true name?",
    "correct_answer":"Amy",
    "difficulty":"Hard",
    "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"How many fatui harbingers are there?",
    "correct_answer":"11",
    "difficulty":"Easy",
    "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What's the name of Jeans burst?",
    "correct_answer":"Dandelion Breeze",
    "difficulty":"Medium",
    "category":"Genshin"
    
  },
  { "question":"What is the Wanderers codename?",
    "correct_answer":"Balladeer",
    "difficulty":"Medium",
    "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is Baizhus weapon called?",
    "correct_answer":"Jadefall Splendor",
    "difficulty":"Medium",
    "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"is Keqing an adeptus?",
    "correct_answer":"False",
    "difficulty":"Easy",
    "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is Beidous crew called?",
  "correct_answer":"The Crux",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"What is Albedo?",
  "correct_answer":"A synthetic human",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"What patch did yelan come out?",
  "correct_answer":"2.8",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"What was the longest banner?",
  "correct_answer":"Ayaka rerun",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"How Long was Ayakas second banner?",
  "correct_answer":"42 days",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"Who were the first two characters on a double banner?",
  "correct_answer":"Albedo and Eula",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"Who had the fastest rerun?",
  "correct_answer":"Yoimiya",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"Which was the First event with lore?",
  "correct_answer":"Unreconciled stars",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"Where can you find the skyfrost nails?",
  "correct_answer":"Dragonspine and the Chasm",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"Which nation worships lord Barbatos?",
  "correct_answer":"Mondstadt",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"What nation does the Adventurer's Guild originate from?",
  "correct_answer":"Snezhnaya",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"How many primogems do you receive for completing the Character Test Run?",
  "correct_answer":"20",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"How many types of chests are there?",
  "correct_answer":"5",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"What reaction does Pyro and Electro make?",
  "correct_answer":"Overload",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"What was the first weapon acquired from an event?",
  "correct_answer":"Festering Desire",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"In which domain can players relive the battle against the fatui harbinger Childe?",
  "correct_answer":"Enter the Golden House",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"How many crowns could you have given traveller from the start to now?",
  "correct_answer":"16",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"Who is the 3rd free character you receive going through the story?",
  "correct_answer":"Lisa",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"Who is the 2nd free character you receive going through the story?",
  "correct_answer":"kaeya",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"Who is the first character the traveller sees in their journey excluding Paimon?",
  "correct_answer":"Venti",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"How did Teppei die?",
  "correct_answer":"A fatui delusion",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"What region has the most chapters in the archon quest?",
  "correct_answer":"Sumeru",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"Where is Dainsleif from?",
  "correct_answer":"Khaenri'ah",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"How much atk did traveller gain from forbidden knowledge?",
  "correct_answer":"3",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who was the first Dendro Archon?",
  "correct_answer":"Greater Lord Rukkhadevata",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }, 
  { "question":"What quantity of a local specialty does a character need to reach level 90?",
  "correct_answer":"168",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is the name of the world inside Raiden Ei's mind?",
  "correct_answer":"The Plane of Euthymia",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who are the characters that uses dendrobiums for ascension?",
  "correct_answer":"Kujou Sara & Chiori",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who was the first character with the ability to perform a mid-air elemental skill?",
  "correct_answer":"Xiao",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },

  { "question":"What are the two opposing energies that the Arkhe system is composed of?",
  "correct_answer":"Pneuma and Ousia ",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who is Childe's master?",
  "correct_answer":"Skirk",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who was the first male electro character released after Razor?",
  "correct_answer":"Cyno",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is the highest crit rate % an artifact can have as a substat?",
  "correct_answer":"23.3",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What item is required to level up a talent to its max?",
  "correct_answer":"Crown of Insight",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who is the only four-star character that has a close up cut-in during their elemental burst?",
  "correct_answer":"Barbara",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which weapon is not wielded by any Archon so far?",
  "correct_answer":"Claymore",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Where is Chiori from?",
  "correct_answer":"Inazuma",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who is known as the Star of Zubayr Theatre?",
  "correct_answer":"Nilou",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which group of weapons have a chance to reset a character's skill cooldown?",
  "correct_answer":"Sacrificial",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is the highest base atk on any weapon?",
  "correct_answer":"741",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which character has the highest base ATK?",
  "correct_answer":"Navia",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What Character Level-Up Material does Rhodeia of Loch drop?",
  "correct_answer":"Cleansing Heart",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is the most expensive item one can purchase from Tubby?",
  "correct_answer":"Transient Resin",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"How much adeptal energy is needed to max out Realm currency accumulation rate?",
  "correct_answer":"20000",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"How much realm currency can be accumulated per hour?",
  "correct_answer":"30",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which elite enemy drops Chilled Meat?",
  "correct_answer":"The Great Snowboar King",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"The Black Serpents are exclusive to which region of the map?",
  "correct_answer":"The Chasm: Underground Mines",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Where is The Knave from?",
  "correct_answer":"Fontaine",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is the cost of a four-star character in Paimon's Bargains?",
  "correct_answer":"34 Masterless Starglitter",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"How many weapons can exclusively be found through exploration alone?",
  "correct_answer":"11",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is the most common local specialty?",
  "correct_answer":"Violet Grass",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is the least common local specialty?",
  "correct_answer":"Silk flowers",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"When is co-op unlocked?",
  "correct_answer":"AR 16",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"How many sides does the dice in Genius invokation TCG have?",
  "correct_answer":"8",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which character gains Physical DMG Bonus from ascending?",
  "correct_answer":"Razor",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who was the first character to be both a playable character and a boss?",
  "correct_answer":"Tartaglia",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Sangonomiya Kokomi is the divine priestess of which island?",
  "correct_answer":"Watatsumi Island",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What do you get from clearing a Domain of Mastery?",
  "correct_answer":"Character Talent Materials",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"How many Shrines of Depths exist in each region?",
  "correct_answer":"10",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What achievement do you receive by exhausting the ten minutes given to complete a bounty?",
  "correct_answer":"Quest failed",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"The creators of Genius Invokation TCG were from where?",
  "correct_answer":"Sumeru",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is the currency used in the Genius Invokation TCG Card Shop?",
  "correct_answer":"Lucky Coins",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which gadget is used to capture animals in order to place them in the Serenitea Pot?",
  "correct_answer":"Omni-Ubiquity Net",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which character has a passive talent related to obtaining wood?",
  "correct_answer":"Arataki Itto",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which event-exclusive 5-star characters do not have a story quest?",
  "correct_answer":"Shenhe & Wanderer",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which character story quests have a name that differs from their character's constellation name?",
  "correct_answer":"Zhongli & Neuvilette",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What character story quests are prerequisites to progress the main Archon quests?",
  "correct_answer":"Kamisato Ayaka, Razor & Yoimiya",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"In which character story quests does the character not appear as a trial character?",
  "correct_answer":"Albedo, Neuvilette & Furina",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who was the first character to have a hangout and a story quest?",
  "correct_answer":"Kaeya",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which non-archon character was the first to get a second story chapter?",
  "correct_answer":"Yoimiya",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"When was the last 4-star character story quest added?",
  "correct_answer":"version 1.0",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which weapon's attack scales with the number of Melusines you've helped?",
  "correct_answer":"\"Ultimate Overlord's Mega Magic Sword\"",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which artifact set has a 2 piece bonus that increases CRIT Rate?",
  "correct_answer":"Berserker",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which character has the lowest Elemental Skill cooldown?",
  "correct_answer":"Lisa",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is the energy cost of the most expensive elemental burst?",
  "correct_answer":"90",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Where did Egeria die during the cataclysm?",
  "correct_answer":"Tunigi Hollow",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which common enemy does not drop anything?",
  "correct_answer":"Cicins",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What kind of enemies have lower resistance to Physical DMG?",
  "correct_answer":"Human enemies",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What are the race of plant-like forest spirits in Sumeru called?",
  "correct_answer":"Aranara",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"How many Visions were seized by the Vision Hunt Decree?",
  "correct_answer":"99",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"How many enemies can drop Recruit's Insignia?",
  "correct_answer":"9",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which weapon material has the most uses?",
  "correct_answer":"Boreal Wolf",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which material has the most uses?",
  "correct_answer":"Slime Condensate",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"How many things, excluding cooking, can Slime Condensate be used for?",
  "correct_answer":"30",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which playable character apart from the Traveler does not have a signature dish?",
  "correct_answer":"Raiden Shogun",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which Forging Material can be mined only in Dragonspine?",
  "correct_answer":"Starsilver",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which Forging Material is found exclusively in Inazuma?",
  "correct_answer":"Amethyst Lumps",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Hu Tao is the 77th Director of _____",
  "correct_answer":"The Wangsheng Funeral Parlor",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What was the name of the contraption that delivered judgement in Fontaine's Opera Epiclese for 500 years?",
  "correct_answer":"The Oratrice Mecanique d'Analyse Cardinale",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which characters do not showcase visible breath when exposed to Sheer Cold in Dragonspine?",
  "correct_answer":"Raiden Shogun and The Wanderer",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Neuvillette and Apep fall under which faction of beings?",
  "correct_answer":"Sovereigns",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What item is required to activate characters' constellations? (except traveler)",
  "correct_answer":"Stella Fortuna",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which character's passive talent reduces their CRIT Rate to a negative value?",
  "correct_answer":"Sangonomiya Kokomi",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which Normal Boss drops the item \"Dew of Repudiation?\"",
  "correct_answer":"Hydro Hypostasis",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What Weekly Boss do you have to defeat to max Aloy's talents?",
  "correct_answer":"La Signora",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which characters wear a fake Vision?",
  "correct_answer":"Venti and Zhongli",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"How many artifact sets have a 2-piece effect of +18% ATK?",
  "correct_answer":"7",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who's signature dish is \"Dizziness-Be-Gone no Jutsu Version 2.0?\"",
  "correct_answer":"Sayu",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"How many character cards can you have in a Genius Invokation TCG deck?",
  "correct_answer":"3",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which playable character has an aquabus line named after them?",
  "correct_answer":"Navia",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which character's Elemental Burst has the longest cooldown?",
  "correct_answer":"Yae Miko",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which playable Archon has the cheapest Elemental Burst?",
  "correct_answer":"Zhongli",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who is the only 5-star character to have two distinct versions of an Elemental Burst?",
  "correct_answer":"Tartaglia",
  "difficulty":"Easy",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who got a vision first between lyney and lynette?",
  "correct_answer":"Lynette",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which living being used to have homes in the dark sea?",
  "correct_answer":"Seelies",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What place is known as the Sea of Ashes?",
  "correct_answer":"Mare Jivari",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Is Lisa part of the Hexenzirkel?",
  "correct_answer":"False",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is Raiden Ei's demon name?",
  "correct_answer":"Beelzebul",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is the name of the Darshan with the largest number of researchers?",
  "correct_answer":"Amurta",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"How did Kaveh's father die?",
  "correct_answer":"Quicksand in the desert",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who is the God of Salt",
  "correct_answer":"Havria",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who was the White Knight in Mondstadt history?",
  "correct_answer":"The Bloodstained Knight",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is another name for vision wielders?",
  "correct_answer":"Allogenes",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who is Vedrfolnir?",
  "correct_answer":"A visionary",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who said these words to the Traveler: The world you once knew is but dust, and the wonders you knew but rubble. Though you should have your own world, and your own people — lamenting what is already lost...?",
  "correct_answer":"K.K.",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is the Kätzlein bloodline known for apart from their feline features?",
  "correct_answer":"Their hunting prowess",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which character once tried to weigh a vision?",
  "correct_answer":"Yanfei",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which artifact set has lore about Tsurumi Island?",
  "correct_answer":"Thundering fury",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which playable character suffers from pumpkin phobia (fear of pumpkins)?",
  "correct_answer":"Lisa",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who tricked the Locals into Unsealing Tartarigami on Yashiori island?",
  "correct_answer":"Nathan",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is the element of Bosacius, Indarius, Bonanus and Menogias respectively?",
  "correct_answer":"Electro, Pyro, Hydro, Geo",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Who taught Aberaku about the Dainichi Mikoshi?",
  "correct_answer":"Kairos",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"The Viridescent Arrow Feather is of which bird?",
  "correct_answer":"Falcon",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Is it true that Amenoma, Isshin, Futsu, Hyakume, and Senju were all once part of the prestigious Raiden Gokaden school of swordsmithing?",
  "correct_answer":"True",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is another name for the Abyss?",
  "correct_answer":"The void realm",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What are the Aquabus lines, Clementine and Callas named after?",
  "correct_answer":"Navia's family",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Where did Remus first appear?",
  "correct_answer":"The primordial sea",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is the adeptus name of Ping?",
  "correct_answer":"Streetward Rambler",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"How long was Tartaglia trapped in the Abyss when he first fell in?",
  "correct_answer":"3 months abyss time, 3 days teyvat time",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Did hilichurls exist before the Khaenri'ahn cataclysm?",
  "correct_answer":"True",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What can be seen in visions and by the people who ascended to celestia?",
  "correct_answer":"A helix-shaped ladder",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What in Genshin Impact is also known as \"God's eye\"?",
  "correct_answer":"A Vision",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What was the title of Frederica in the knights of Favonius?",
  "correct_answer":"Alder knight",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is another name for Khaenri'ah?",
  "correct_answer":"Dahri",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"What is the correct order of Samsara cycles according to the Narzissenkreuz ordo?",
  "correct_answer":"Hyperborea, Natlantean, Remuria, Khraun-Arya",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which elemental ascension stone differs from the rest thematically?",
  "correct_answer":"Cryo gem stone",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"From who did Yelan intercept a delivery from to make her coat",
  "correct_answer":"The Tsaritsa",
  "difficulty":"Hard",
  "category":"Genshin"
  },
  { "question":"Which character(s) have no Invincibility Frames on their burst",
  "correct_answer":"Fischl",
  "difficulty":"Medium",
  "category":"Genshin"
  }
]
